A book or a book?
お帳か、お帳やっか
There will also be appetizers.
お通しもあるだろう
Do you know what this is?
これ何だかわかるか?
money.
お金
That's the kind of money you like.
お前好きなお金だよな
I'll put what you like and what's most important to you.
お前の好きなもん、一番大事なとこ入れてやるわ
Add it, add it.
足しろよ、足しろ
Hide your hands, it's on.
手隠せ、かかってなって
It's a hindrance.
邪魔だっそ
This is a piggy bank.
貯金箱だな、これが
How much money have you earned so far?
これでお前、今までいくら稼いだんだよ
これでお前、今までいくら稼いだんだよ、
This idiot.
このアバカツだよ
How much did you earn?
いくら稼いだんだ?
I wonder if he's doing it so much that I don't understand.
分かんないくらいやってんのか、ちょっと
You don't know whether it's a dick or money.
お前、チンコか金か分かんないだろな
Handle it.
手どけ
Hey, turn this way.
ほら、こっち向けよ
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいいんだろ?
Is it true?
本当か?
Which phone call did you feel better about earlier?
さっきの電話、どっちが気持ちよかった?
I felt better on the phone.
電話のほうが気持ちよかったです
I'm going to have a little more fun with you today.
今日もっとお前、ちょっと楽しませるわ
You're a university student.
お前が大学生だよな
yes.
はい
You're a university student.
お前大学生だよな
yes.
はい
Well then, you should at least memorize this technique.
じゃあ、ちょっとこれの技ぐらい覚えておいたほうがいいん
Isn't it?
じゃない の?
Isn't that so?
そうだよね?
Okay?
いいよか?
Let's try it first.
まずは、やってみよう
Try it out.
出してみろ
A little more, a little more.
もうちょい、もうちょい
Isn't that enough?
余裕じゃね?
Shall we do the next attraction?
次のアトラクションやっちゃう?
I'll open this next time.
次、これ開くんだな
Please wake up, please.
ちゃんとお前、顔起こせよ
Get on your knees and wake up.
ひじついて、状態を起こして
When I leave, I say I'll leave, properly.
出るとき、出しますって言うよ、ちゃんと
Yes, I'll take it out.
はい、出します
I think you're making a habit of it.
くせぇしてんじゃねーか
One more time, one more time.
もう一回、もう一回だよ
Are you doing it next time?
次にもやってるか?
Is it fun?
楽しいか?
Is this really fun?
本当に楽しいのか、これが?
So it's the real M.
じゃあ、本当のMだな
The decisive moment is too late.
決定的瞬間、遅いから
me too?
私も?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, properly.
じゃあ、ちゃんと
It's a good piggy bank, isn't it?
いい貯金箱じゃねーかよ
Where did you learn it?
どこで覚えたんだよ
Well, let me clean it up a bit.
じゃあ、ちょっときよめてやるか
Cleanse me.
きよめてさ
Will you cleanse your money here?
ここで金きよめる?
Are you not going out?
出ねーのか?
I can't go out.
出ねーの
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよな
Well, I want you to do more.
じゃあ、もっとやってほしいよな
Well then, let's raise it.
じゃあ、上げていこうか
yes.
はい
Also, make sure you follow the bolt properly.
また、お前、ちゃんとボルトでついておめ
What is this? Do you understand?
これ、なんだ、わかるか?
Look, this.
ほら、これ
Well then, what should we do with that?
じゃあ、これで、あそこを何しろ
leg hair.
足の毛
I just looked at the camera and did it.
ちゃんとカメラ見てんで、すんだよ
Are you feeling better?
気持ちよくなってきたか
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいか?
yes.
はい
I can't see well.
よく見えない
Hey, let's make a piece with both hands.
おい、両手でピースしよう
yes.
はい
Hey, look.
ちょ、見て
How would you feel if you were sent to wait for a while?
ちょっと待ちに送られたらどう思うんですか?
Are you being watched?
見られてーのか?
This is what it looks like.
こんな姿
I don't like it.
嫌です
It feels good right now.
今のときに気持ちいい
say something
何か言う
I don't like it.
嫌です
I could say thank you for cleansing me.
きよめてくれて、ありがとうございますと言えたりと
Thank you for cleansing me.
きよめてくれて、ありがとうございます
Well then, you.
じゃあ、お前
It also cleansed my upper mouth.
上の口もきよめてくれた
It's getting shallower again.
また浅くなってんじゃん
Is it Manpe's Tsuruget?
マンペのツルゲットかよ
What is it, what is it?
なんだよ、なんだよ
What is it?
なんだよ
Manpe?
マンペ?
What's going on with this mouth?
こっちの口でもなんのか?
Is it Manpe's Tsuruget?
マンペのツルゲットかよ
This hair.
こっちの毛よ
Don't get too low.
下抜くなよ
You're like an instrument.
お前なんか楽器みたいになってるぞ
You're like a musical instrument, aren't you?
お前楽器みたいになってんじゃねーかよ
Get it down.
下ろせ
You're already looking good, aren't you?
もういい顔してきたじゃねーか
Yo.
よ
Don't you want it?
欲 しくねーのか?
Don't you need it?
いらねーのか
Hirate.
ひらて
Open your legs.
足ひらてよ
Did you bring something out now?
何か出したか、今
Sorry.
すいません
Don't go on your own.
勝手に行くな
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Move it yourself, here.
自分で動かせ、ほら
Don't make a fuss.
キャンキャン、キャンキャン、騒ぐんじゃねーよ
You've been coughing.
せき込んできたねーよ
Don't cough.
せき込むなよ
It's a reward jack.
ご褒美のジャッキだ
How about a jack as a reward?
ご褒美のジャッキどうだ?
What do you think?
どうなんだよ
The jack as a reward is delicious.
美味しいかな、ご褒美のジャッキは
Look.
ほ ら
Here, come in.
ほ ら、入れよ
Then you put it in properly.
そしたらお前、ちゃんと入れろ
You're fine.
お前気上いで
You're good.
お前上手いじゃん
That's right.
そうだよ
Well then, it's jack time for your reward.
じゃあご褒美のジャッキタイムだな
Show me where you're going.
行くとこ見せろ
Hey, I guess you have something to say.
おい、言うことあるんだろ
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
Say it.
言えよ
I guess they let me out.
出してもらったんだろ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Get on your elbows.
ひじついて
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
Please let me in.
入れてくださいよと
Please put it in.
入れてください
I asked him to put it in doggy style.
ワンちゃんスタイルで入れてくださいよとした
Please put it in.
入れてください
Elbow.
ひじつけ
Hey, look.
おい、ほら
Become the fourth again.
また四つ目になれ
Well then, we had fun.
じゃあ、俺ら楽しましちゃったから
I'll delete the previous video.
前 の動画は消してやるよ
I won't delete Monty though.
モンティは消さないけど
Good.
よかったな
1 item entered and 1 item increased.
1個入って1個増えた